netsob.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Netsob Help Centre

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Netsob. Sometimes we may post product-specific privacy notices or Help Centre materials to explain our products in more detail.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://help.netsob.com/contact/).

**Information that we collect and how we use it**

We may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information that you provide** – When you sign up for an account with one of our website, we ask you for personal information. We may combine the information that you submit under your account with information from other Netsob services in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.
  * **Cookies** – When you visit any Netsob website, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including storing user preferences, improving search results and tracking user trends. Netsob also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads on Netsob services.
  * **Log information** – When you access Netsob services via a browser, application or other client, our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.
  * **User communications** – When you send emails or other communications to Netsob, we may retain those communications in order to process your enquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. When you send and receive SMS messages to or from one of our services that provides SMS functionality, we may collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the wireless operator associated with the phone number, the content of the message as well as the date and time of the transaction. We may use your email address or phone number to communicate with you about our services.
  * **Third-Party Applications** – Netsob may make available third-party applications, such as gadgets or extensions, through its services. The information collected by Netsob when you enable a third-party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third-party application provider is governed by their privacy policies.
  * **Location data** – Netsob offers location-enabled services. If you use those services, Netsob may receive information about your actual location (such as GPS signals sent by a mobile device) or information that can be used to approximate a location (such as a mobile ID).

In addition to the above, we may use the information that we collect to:

  * Provide, maintain, protect and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services; and
  * Protect the rights or property of Netsob or our users.

If we use this information in a manner different to the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

**Choices**

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Netsob features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**Information sharing**

Netsob only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside Netsob in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require these parties to agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Netsob, its users or the public, as required or permitted by law.

If Netsob becomes involved in a merger, acquisition or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Netsob employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use Netsob services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request, if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes) or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except when doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way that we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our back-up systems.

**Enforcement**

Netsob regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is Netsob’s policy to contact the complainant regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Netsob and an individual.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).

Last Updated on 17th July, 2014.
